Zhiyi, are you okay
تشيي، هل أنت بخير؟
Cheng Yadong
تشنغ يادونغ
I really did not expect it
لم أتوقع ذلك حقاً
you could do something like this
يمكنك فعل شيء كهذا
I was forced
أُجبرت
Xie Jiachang has gone crazy
لقد أصيب Xie Jiachang بالجنون
Where is A Qiang
أين آ تشيانغ؟
I am asking you, where is A Qiang
أسألكم، أين آ تشيانغ؟
I do not know where A Qiang is
لا أعرف أين آ تشيانغ
Tell me honestly
أخبرني بصراحة
Locked up by that Xie
محبوس من قبل ذلك شي
No matter what
مهما كان الأمر
whatever it costs today
مهما كانت التكلفة اليوم
I will get you out safely
سأخرجك سالماً
Trust me
ثق بي
Go
يذهب
Go (Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org)
انتقل (ادعم المشرف، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org)
A Shan, A-Quan
أ شان، أ-كوان
Boss
رئيس
Where are the other brothers
أين الإخوة الآخرون؟
The brothers are busy at Warehouse No. 4
الأخوان مشغولان في المستودع رقم 4
Xie Jiachang is mad
Xie Jiachang مجنون
We cannot stay at the dock
لا يمكننا البقاء في الرصيف
Call the brothers and pull out fast
اتصل بالإخوة وانطلق بسرعة
Yes
نعم
Boss, I will lead the way
سيدي، سأقود الطريق
Go
يذهب
Well, well
حسناً، حسناً
That cigar of yours is not bad
سيجارك ليس سيئاً
You dare betray me
أتجرؤ على خيانتي؟
Why split you and me
لماذا نفرق بيني وبينك؟
We are all brothers
كلنا إخوة
Boss Xie
الرئيس شي
This woman tried to run
حاولت هذه المرأة الركض
I dragged her back
سحبتها إلى الخلف
Really
حقًا
Then sorry to trouble you, Boss Cheng
إذن، آسف على الإزعاج، أيها الرئيس تشنغ
Then do me a favor and tie her back up
ثم أسدِ لي معروفاً وقم بربطها مرة أخرى
Cheng Yadong
تشنغ يادونغ
What am I supposed to say to you
ماذا يفترض بي أن أقول لك؟
After all these years
بعد كل هذه السنوات
Haven't you done enough lousy things
ألم تفعل ما يكفي من الأشياء السيئة؟
Ah
آه
Why grow a conscience now
لماذا ننمي ضميرنا الآن؟
Too late
فات الأوان
Boss Xie
الرئيس شي
I owe Zhou Zhiyi too much
أنا مدين لـ تشو تشيي بالكثير
Let her go
اسمح لها أن تذهب
I will stay with you
سأبقى معك
Is it okay to go after Zheng Nanfeng
هل يجوز ملاحقة تشنغ نانفنغ؟
Touched
تأثرت
So touched
تأثرت كثيراً
Fine
بخير
For your devotion
تقديراً لتفانيكم
I promise you
أعدك
You
أنت
call Zheng Nanfeng
اتصل بـ تشنغ نانفنغ
Tell him to come
أخبره أن يأتي
As long as he comes
طالما أنه يأتي
I will let Zhou Zhiyi go
سأترك تشو تشي يي يذهب
The two of us brothers will stay to take on Zheng Nanfeng
سنبقى نحن الأخوين لمواجهة تشنغ نانفنغ
How about it
ما رأيك؟
Okay
تمام
Cheng Yadong, don't
تشنغ يادونغ، لا تفعل
Come here
تعال الى هنا
Don't
لا
This is Zheng Nanfeng
هذا هو تشنغ نانفنغ
Zheng Nanfeng
تشنغ نانفنغ
Zhou Zhiyi is at the dock warehouse
تشو تشي يي موجود في مستودع الميناء
Don't listen to him
لا تستمع إليه
If you want to save her
إذا كنت تريد إنقاذها
Brother Chang is here waiting for you
الأخ تشانغ هنا في انتظارك
Brother Chang
الأخ تشانغ
I want you, Brother Chang
أريدك يا ​​أخي تشانغ
to betray me
أن تخونني
Zhou Zhiyi
تشو تشيي
I will step out to handle something
سأخرج لأتعامل مع شيء ما.
You know me
أنت تعرفني
There is no way I will not go
لا سبيل لعدم الذهاب
This time is not like usual
هذه المرة ليست كالمعتاد
I do not want to drag the brothers down
لا أريد أن أتسبب في إحباط الإخوة
Drag down what
اسحب لأسفل ما
You are ditching me on purpose now
أنت تتخلى عني عن قصد الآن
Are you trying to tear down my
هل تحاول هدم مشروعي؟
Loyal and Righteous banner
راية الولاء والصلاح
If I do not come back this time
إذا لم أعد هذه المرة
do not blame me
لا تلومني
If I cannot, you carry me back
إذا لم أستطع، فأعدني إلى الوراء.
Why has he not come yet
لماذا لم يأتِ بعد؟
Does he not want you anymore
هل لم يعد يريدك؟
Xie Jiachang
شيه جياتشانغ
I am here
أنا هنا
He really came
لقد جاء بالفعل
Your Brother Nanfeng came to save you
جاء أخوك نانفنغ لإنقاذك
Open your eyes wide and watch closely
افتح عينيك على اتساعهما وانظر عن كثب
how I kill him
كيف أقتله
Let her go
اسمح لها أن تذهب
Let go
اتركه
Kill him
اقتله
Nanfeng
نانفينج
I'm here
أنا هنا
Nanfeng, hurry, go!
نانفينج، أسرع، اذهب!
A Ming, go
مينغ، اذهب
Go
يذهب
Don't let him get away, chase!
لا تدعه يفلت، طارده!
A Ming
أ مينغ
Go!
يذهب!
Go
يذهب
A Ming
أ مينغ
Nanfeng
نانفينج
Hurry, go!
أسرع، انطلق!
A Ming
أ مينغ
Go
يذهب
Do we really have to go?
هل علينا الذهاب حقاً؟
Are you really ditching me now on purpose?
هل تتخلى عني الآن عن قصد؟
Are you trying to ruin my loyal and righteous reputation?
هل تحاول تشويه سمعتي المخلصة والنزيهة؟
I
أنا
Du Wenming
دو ونمينغ
Loyal
وفي
and
و
righ-
ملِك-
teous
teous
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine
أنا بخير
Go
يذهب
Hurry, go!
أسرع، انطلق!
Nanfeng
نانفينج
Go
يذهب
Out of the way!
ابتعد عن الطريق!
Nanfeng
نانفينج
Get out!
اخرج!
Get out
اخرج
Nanfeng
نانفينج
Let go of me
دعني أذهب
Run
يجري
Run!
يجري!
Think you can run?
هل تعتقد أنك تستطيع الركض؟
You're all dead
أنتم جميعاً أموات
Xie Jiachang, let go of me
شيه جياتشانغ، اتركني
Xie Jiachang
شيه جياتشانغ
Don't move
لا تتحرك
Take one more step and I'll kill her
خطوة أخرى وسأقتلها
Let my wife go
دع زوجتي تذهب
What you want is my life
ما تريده هو حياتي
I'll give you my life
سأهب لك حياتي
Fine
بخير
You piece of trash
يا لك من حثالة!
Jump off!
اقفز!
Nanfeng, don't!
نانفينج، لا تفعل!
Even if you jump, he won't let us go
حتى لو قفزت، فلن يتركنا نذهب
Do you remember what I told you
هل تتذكر ما قلته لك؟
The story of another world?
قصة عالم آخر؟
Maybe this is my fate
ربما هذا هو قدري
Jump for me
اقفز من أجلي
I said jump!
قلت اقفز!
Nanfeng, don't!
نانفينج، لا تفعل!
If you don't jump, I'll kill her
إذا لم تقفز، فسأقتلها
No!
لا!
Xie Jiachang
شيه جياتشانغ
Remember what you said
تذكر ما قلته
Or even as a ghost, I'll kill you
أو حتى كشبح، سأقتلك
Zheng Nanfeng
تشنغ نانفنغ
If there is a next life,
إذا كانت هناك حياة أخرى،
I don't want to meet you again
لا أريد أن أراك مرة أخرى
Zhiyi
تشيي
No!
لا!
Nanfeng, don't jump
نانفينج، لا تقفز
Zheng Nanfeng, don't!
تشنغ نانفنغ، لا تفعل!
No!
لا!
Don't jump
لا تقفز
I love you
أحبك
Nanfeng
نانفينج
Don't jump
لا تقفز
No!
لا!
Zheng Nanfeng
تشنغ نانفنغ
Starting today,
ابتداءً من اليوم،
I won't let you suffer even the slightest grievance
لن أدعك تعاني ولو من أدنى قدر من الظلم.
I'll never let you down again in this life
لن أخذلكم مرة أخرى في هذه الحياة
I love you
أحبك
Me too
أنا أيضاً
Nanfeng
نانفينج
You two have been cold with each other for 49 days
لقد كنتما باردين مع بعضكما البعض لمدة 49 يومًا
Is this ever going to end or what?
هل سينتهي هذا الأمر يوماً ما أم ماذا؟
Hey
يا
Yanhong
يانهونغ
Your technique is not what it used to be
أسلوبك لم يعد كما كان.
What is up with you?
ما الذي يحدث معك؟
Tomorrow is Master Qin's 66th birthday banquet
غداً هو حفل عشاء بمناسبة عيد ميلاد المعلم تشين السادس والستين
The cafe owner across the street
صاحب المقهى المقابل
Liu Shijie and A-Chang will both come
سيحضر كل من ليو شيجي وآ تشانغ
They are our arch-enemies
إنهم أعداؤنا اللدودون
Do not let them laugh at us again
لا تدعهم يسخرون منا مرة أخرى
Eat well and drink well
تناول طعامًا جيدًا واشرب جيدًا
Still mad?
ما زلت غاضباً؟
Come on, you two are an old married couple
هيا، أنتما زوجان متزوجان منذ فترة طويلة
Wife
زوجة
Watch what you say
انتبه لما تقول
Who are you calling your wife?
من تنادي زوجتك؟
No
لا
You slept with me
لقد نمت معي
And you will not take responsibility?
ولن تتحمل المسؤولية؟
You, let me tell you—
أنت، دعني أخبرك؟
Do you know you were wrong?
هل تعلم أنك كنت مخطئاً؟
I...
أنا...
Xie Jiachang
شيه جياتشانغ
I was wrong
كنت مخطئًا
I...
أنا...
I should love you a little more than I do now
ينبغي أن أحبك أكثر قليلاً مما أحبك الآن
You had better
كان لديك أفضل
I know
أنا أعرف
No
لا
You—
أنت؟؟؟
Youyou
أنت
Give me a kiss
أعطني قبلة
Come on, give me a kiss
هيا، أعطني قبلة
I miss you
أفتقدك
Whenever dusk falls
كلما حل الغسق
The evening breeze rises
نسيم المساء يهب
I miss you
أفتقدك
Life's answer
إجابة الحياة
Try not to see it clearly
حاول ألا تراه بوضوح
Close your eyes
أغمض عينيك
Do not answer
لا تجب
The evening breeze blows and blows
تهب نسائم المساء وتهب
Go with the wind
انطلق مع الريح
Tonight, children, do not cry in secret
الليلة يا أطفال، لا تبكوا سراً
Do not cry in secret
لا تبكِ في السر
The evening breeze blows and blows
تهب نسائم المساء وتهب
Go with the wind
انطلق مع الريح
With the nightfall and the stars
مع حلول الليل وظهور النجوم
Drift gently to sleep
انسي بهدوء حتى تغفو
Feel the evening breeze
استمتع بنسيم المساء